Narrator: Before dinner, Gordon had a drink with Jeremy in the library.
Gordon: Cheers, Jeremy. Happy Birthday.
Jeremy: Ah, thanks, Gordon.
Gordon: Listen, Jeremy, I want to talk to you about Barbara.
Jeremy: Barbara?
What’s the problem?
Gordon: It’s not exactly a problem.
I’m in love with her, and I want to marry her.
Jeremy: Marry Barbara? Marry my daughter!
Are you crazy? Never! You don’t love Barbara.
You only want her money!
Gordon: That’s not true, Jeremy.
I love her.
Jeremy: Listen to me.
If you marry Barbara, when I die all my money goes to Claudia.
Gordon: To Claudia? To your secretary?
Jeremy: Yes.
Gordon: Is that your last word, Jeremy?
Jeremy: Yes, it is.
Cook: Dinner everybody!
Narrator: At midnight Gordon was in the living room.
He finished his whisky and went upstairs.
Jeremy: Who is it?
Gordon?
What are you…